Booth Tarkington Papers, 1812-1956 (bulk 1899-1946): Finding Aid C0062
Manuscripts Division
- Series 3: Correspondence, 1880-1952; 47 boxes
  - Subseries 3A: From Tarkington, 1881-1952; 25 boxes
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1944; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 1)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1945; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 2)
    - Street, Julian Sr., 1946 and undated; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 3)
    - Street, Margot (Mrs. Julian Street, Sr.), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 4)
    - Street, Julian, Jr. (Pete), 1935-1946; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 5)
    - Street, Amanda (Pete Street's daughter), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 183, Folder 6)
    - T, circa 1939-1944; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 1)
    - Taggart, Lucy, 1922-1943; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 2)
    - Taggart, Lucy, 1944-1945; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Tarkington, Elizabeth (Mrs. John S. - Mother), 1881-1900; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 4)
    - Tarkington, Elizabeth (Mother), 1901-1905; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Tarkington, Elizabeth (Mother), 1906-1909; 1 folder (Box 184, Folder 6)
    - Tarkington, John S. (Father), 1881-1900; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 1)
    - Tarkington, John S. (Father), 1901-1906; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 2)
    - Tarkington, John S. (Father), 1907-1910; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Tarkington, John S. (Father), 1911-1916; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 4)
    - Tarkington, John S. (Father), 1917-1919; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 5)
    - Tarkington, John S. (Father), 1920-1921; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Tarkington, John S. (Father), 1922; 1 folder (Box 185, Folder 7)
    - Tarkington, Mr. & Mrs. John S. (Parents), 1887-1905; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 1)
    - Tarkington, Mr. & Mrs. John S. (Parents), 1895-1898; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 2)
    - Tarkington, Mr. & Mrs. John S. (Parents), 1899-1900; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 3)
    - Tarkington, Mr. & Mrs. John S. (Parents), 1905-1909; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 4)
    - Tarkington, Laurel, 1911-1922; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 5)
    - Tarkington, Susanah, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 6)
    - Tarkington, Linda (Mrs. John S. - stepmother), 1922-1935; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 7)
    - Tarkington, Linda, 1936-1943; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 8)
    - Thompson, Jack, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 9)
    - Toohey, John P., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 186, Folder 10)
    - Trotter, Miss Elizabeth (Betty) (secretary), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 1)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H. (Elizabeth - Betty's mother), 1923-1925; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 2)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H., 1926-1927; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H., 1928-1931; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H., 1932-1934; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 5)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H., 1935-1938; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 6)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H., 1939; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 7)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H., 1940; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 8)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H., 1941-1944; 1 folder (Box 187, Folder 9)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H., undated; 1 folder (Box 188, Folder 1)
    - Trotter, Mrs. William H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 188, Folder 2)
    - Tyler, George, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 188, Folder 3)
    - V, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Vose, Robert C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - W, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Wallace, Warrack, 1933-1938; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 4)
    - Wallace, Warrack, 1939-1941; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - Wallace, Warrack, 1942; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 6)
    - Wallace, Warrack, 1943; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Wallace, Warrack, 1944; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Wallace, Warrack, 1945; 1 folder (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - Wallick, John, 1905-1926; 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 1)
    - Wallick, John, 1930-1940; 1 folder (Box 190, Folder 2)
    - Warner, Aucher, 1932-1935; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Warner, Aucher and wife, Maudie, 1936-1937; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Warner, Aucher and wife, Maudie, 1938; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Warner, Aucher, 1939; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Warner, Aucher, 1940-1943; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 5)
    - Warner, Aucher, undated; 1 folder (Box 191, Folder 6)
    - Wetherell, Howard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 1)
    - X, Y, Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 3)
    - Fragments, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 4)
    - Unidentified, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3B: To Tarkington, 1880-1946; 22 boxes
    Consists of letters received by Tarkington from individuals and organizations such as the American Academy of Arts and Letters, Doubleday and Co., Dr. Carl McCulloch, and Society for the Prevention of W.W. III, as well as others.
    - Ab - Am, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Acheson, Cornell W. (nephew), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 2)
    - Ade, George, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 3)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 4)
    - American Magazine, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 5)
    - Ames, Elizabeth (cousin), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 6)
    - An - Ay, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Ansonnini, Antonio, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Ba - Boni, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Berheimer, Earle J., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - (The) Bobbs - Merrill Co., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Book News, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - Booth, Fenton W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - Booth - Brotaw, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Brandt, Carl, of Brandt & Brandt, 1931-1941; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - Brandt, Carl, 1942-1946; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 16)
    - Brazington, W. C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 193, Folder 17)
    - Brown - Bye, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Brown, Hilton U., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Bullitt, Marshall, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Burrage, Madelaine and Mildred, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Ca - Cl, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - C., W. C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Calkins, D. D., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - (The) Century Magazine, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Children, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Clowes, G. H. A. (Alec.), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Coates - Cox, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Cox, Dora H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 194, Folder 12)
    - Coukling, Ntalie Burleigh, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Cortissoz, Royal, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Cr - Cu, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Currie, Barton, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 4)
    - Curtis, Brow Ltd., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 5)
    - Da - De, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 6)
    - Danniels, Harrison R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 7)
    - Davison, Robert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 8)
    - Deering, Katherine A., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 195, Folder 9)
    - Di - Dw, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Dickson, Harris, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Dorsey, John M. (M.D.), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Doubleday and Co., 1899-1932; 1 folder (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Doubleday and Co., 1933-1946; 1 folder (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - E, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Eggers, George William, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Everybody's Magazine, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 196, Folder 8)
    - Fa - Fl, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Farr, Daniel H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Fesler, Caroline, undated; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Fisher, Howard S. (Mike), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Fletcher, Louisa (Tarkington's 1st wife), 1898-1922; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Fletcher, Louisa, 1923; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Fletcher, Louisa, 1924-1934; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Fo - Fu, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Freedman, Sam, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Ga - Gi, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Garland, Hamlin, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - (The) Great Altantic & Pacific Tea Co., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Gl - Gu, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Ha, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Hale, Robert, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Harper and Brothers, undated; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Hayes, Helen, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Hays, Will H., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - He - Hy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Hengricks, Caroline Butler, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Hibben, John Grier, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Howells, William Dean, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Indiana Committee For National Defense, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - (The) Indianapolis News, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Indianapolis Symphony Orchestra, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - J, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Jackson, Basil R., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Jameson, A-G, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Jameson, Haute (Tarkington's sister), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Jameson, Haute and Ovid, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Jameson, J-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Kahler, Hugh, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Kelly, Fred C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Kyle, Howard, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - La - Li, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Ladies' Home Journal, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Lamont, Thomas W., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Lo - Ly, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Loring, Philip Q., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Ludlow, Louis, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - Lunt, Alfred, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Mac, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Mai - May, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Manship, Paul, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Maurice, Arthur B., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Mc, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - McClure, S. S. (Co.), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Mak, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - McKnight, Harriet E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Me - My, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Miller, Samuel D., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 10)
    - Murray, "Big", dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 201, Folder 11)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1913-1935; 1 folder (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1936-1938; 1 folder (Box 202, Folder 2)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1939-1941; 1 folder (Box 202, Folder 3)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1942-1944; 1 folder (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - McCulloch, Dr. Carl, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Na - Ne, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - (The) National Security League, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 2)
    - National War Fund, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 3)
    - Neall, Adelaide, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 4)
    - New, Harry S., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 5)
    - Newhouse, Bert (Newhouse Galleries), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 6)
    - Ni - Nu, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 7)
    - Nicholson, Meridith, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 8)
    - Norton, Louise D., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 9)
    - O, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 10)
    - Osborn, Chase S., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Pa - Pf, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 12)
    - Panofsky, Erwin, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 13)
    - Parsons, Henry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Ph - Py, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Phelps, William Lyon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Phillips Exeter Academy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Pitkin, Helen, 1893-1897; 1 folder (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Pitkin, Helen, 1899-1900; 1 folder (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Princeton, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Q, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Ra - Ri, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Ro - Ru, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Rogers, Herbert M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 204, Folder 7)
    - Ross, David, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 204, Folder 8)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, 1919-1937; 1 folder (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, 1942-1944; 1 folder (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, 1938-1940; 1 folder (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, 1941; 1 folder (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Roberts, Kenneth, undated; 1 folder (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Sa - Se, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Saturday Evening Post, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - (The) Seeing Eye, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Sh - Sk, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Sheldon, Elenore, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Sigma, Chi, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - Silberman, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - Skinner, Otis, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - Sl - Sq, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - Slims, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - Smith, E. A. P., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - Smith, H. P. (Pratt), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Society for the Prevention of W.W. III, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - St - Sw, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Stark, Jack Gage, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - Strong, Isobel, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - Sutherland, Evelyn Greenleaf, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - Street, Julian, 1912-1929; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Street, Julian, 1930-1939; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Street, Julian, 1940-1942; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Street, Julian, 1943-1946; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Street, Julian, and Street, Pete, undated; 1 folder (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Ta - Th, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Thirkell, Stanley, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - This Week, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Thompson, James Mac N., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 4)
    - Ti - Ty, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 5)
    - Towne, Charles Hanson, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 6)
    - Trotter, Elizabeth, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 7)
    - Trotter, Mr. and Mrs. William H., 1916-1939; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 8)
    - Trotter, Mr. and Mrs. William H., 1940-1945; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 9)
    - Tyler, George C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 209, Folder 10)
    - Tarkington, Charlie, Martha Anne, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Tarkington, Elizabeth (mother), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Tarkington, John S. (father), 1880-1887; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Tarkington, John S., 1888; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Tarkington, John S., 1895-1917; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Tarkington, Laurel, 1913-1919; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 6)
    - Tarkington, Laurel, 1912-1922; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 7)
    - Tarkington, Linda (stepmother), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 8)
    - Tarkington, Susanah (2nd wife), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 210, Folder 9)
    - U, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Committee on Public Information, undated; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - U.S. Library of Congress, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - U.S. Treasury Department, undated; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - United War Fund, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Venturi, Lionello, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 6)
    - Vezin, Charles, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 7)
    - V, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 8)
    - Vose, Robert C., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 9)
    - Wa, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 10)
    - Wallace, Warrack, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 11)
    - Wallick, Frederick, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 12)
    - Warnner, Aucher, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 13)
    - Warner, Mary Alice, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 14)
    - Warnock, Elizabeth M., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 211, Folder 15)
    - Notes, dates not examined; 1 folder Autograph manuscript (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence Concerning Warner Bros. Suit, 1939 February 23 - 1941 October 23; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Penrod and His Twin: Analysis of the Scenario, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Typed Manuscript (Carbon), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Answers to Interrogatory No. II, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Typed Manuscript in Elizabeth Trotter's Hand, undated; 1 folder Carbon (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Plaintiffs Trial Memorandum, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (carbon) (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Plaintiffs Memorandom on Motion to Strike Out, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Defenses and Dismiss Counterclaim, undated; 1 folder (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Bill of Particulars, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (carbon) (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - List of Penrod Stories, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (carbon) (Box 212, Folder 4)
      With manuscript corrections in Elizabeth Trotter's hand.
    - Proposed Interrogatories, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (carbon) (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Answers, undated; 1 folder Typed manuscript (Box 212, Folder 4)
      Manuscript in Elizabeth Trotter's hand.
    - We - Wh, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 1)
    - Wethrell, Howard Gradford, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 2)
    - White, Wa, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 3)
    - Whitmore, Julia, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 4)
    - Wi, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 5)
    - Wicks, Frank, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 6)
    - Willkie, Wendell, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Susan Arlington, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Williams, Jesse Lynch, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Harry Leon, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Wilstach, Paul, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 11)
    - Wo - Wy, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 12)
    - Wolfe, Katharine S., dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 13)
    - Woollcott, Alexander, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 14)
    - Writer's War Bond, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 15)
    - Y, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 16)
    - Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 213, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified (First Name Only), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Unidentified (No Names), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified (Indecipherable), dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 214, Folder 3)
- Series 4: Documents, dates not examined; 1 box
  Consists of miscellaneous documents of Booth Tarkington.
  - Documents, dates not examined; 5 folders (Box 215, Folder 1-5)
- Series 5: Photographs, dates not examined; 5 boxes
  Consists of photographs of Booth Tarkington in his early and later years as well as photographs of his family and friends.
  This series is arranged into five subseries: Tarkington: Early Years, Tarkington: Later Years, Family/Friends, Miscellaneous, and Unidentified.
  - Subseries 5A: Tarkington: Early Years, dates not examined; 1 box
    Consists of photographs of Booth Tarkington during his early years.
    - Tarkington: Early Years, dates not examined; 3 folders (Box 216, Folder 1-3)
  - Subseries 5B: Tarkington: Later Years, dates not examined; 1 box
    Consists of photographs of Booth Tarkington during his later years.
    - Tarkington: Later Years, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 217, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 5C: Family/Friends, dates not examined; 1 box
    Consists of photographs of Booth Tarkington's family and friends.
    - Family/Friends, dates not examined; 14 folders (Box 218, Folder 1-14)
  - Subseries 5D: Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 1 box
    Consists of miscellaneous photographs.
    - Miscellaneous, dates not examined; 10 folders (Box 219, Folder 1-10)
  - Subseries 5E: Unidentified, dates not examined; 1 box
    Consists of various unidentified photographs.
    - Unidentified Persons, dates not examined; 4 folders (Box 220, Folder 1-4)
- Series 6: Memorabilia, dates not examined; 2 boxes
  Consists of the miscellaneous memorabilia of Booth Tarkington.
  - Memorabilia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 221)
  - Scrapbook, 1904; 1 box (Box 221A)
- Series 7: Printed Material/Magazines, 1899 May-1946; 31 boxes
  Consists of magazines, ephemera, and clippings. Some of these include "Cosmopolitan," "Harper's Magazine," and "Ladies Home Journal."
  This series is arranged into three subseries: Magazines, A-Z, Ephemera, and Clippings.
  - Subseries 7A: Magazines, A - Z, 1899 May-1946; 26 boxes
    Consists of magazines collected by Booth Tarkington, such as "The Saturday Evening Post," "Good Housekeeping," and "The Red Book Magazine."
    Arranged alphabetically by publication.
    - A - B, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 222)
    - Ch - Cosmopolitan, 1905 December-1913 December; 1 box (Box 223)
    - Cosmopolitan, 1914 January-1917 April; 1 box (Box 224)